<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TwoActivities_V2_CodingChallenge</string>
    <string name="text_selectOption">Please select the conversation you\'d like to read</string>
    <string name="button_conversation1">convo 1</string>
    <string name="button_conversation2">convo 2</string>
    <string name="button_conversation3">convo 3</string>
    <string name="conversation_1">Frank: yo, wuddup bro?!\n\n
    Chris: BROOOOOOOOOOO, where them bitches at?!\n\n
    Frank: I don\'t know, bro. You\'re the one with the hooks, lines, and sinkers!\n\n
    Chris: Man, you gotta catch the fuck up.\n\n
    Frank: Those are fighting words, bro! I\'m gonna have to beat you up for that one!\n\n
    Chris: BRING! IT! OOOOOOOON, BRO!\n\n
    Frank: Oh, it\'s coming. And when it does, you won\'t even know what hit you, bro!\n\n
    Chris: You have no idea what kind of training I've been through since we\'ve last been together,
    bro! You seriously do not want to start a fight with me!\n\n
    Frank: I could say the same thing to you, my friend! I\'ll see you in the parking lot at 5
    hundred hours! You better be there on time!\n\n
    Chris: Prepare to get your ass handed to you, bro!</string>
    <string name="conversation_2">The Mother: When are you done work tonight?\n\n
    Me: Beats me, lawl.\n\n
    The Mother: Look, buddy boy! I\'m not going to just drop everhthing I\'m doing at the drop of a
    hat if you tell me you\'re clocking out in the moment! Don\'t expect a speedy pick up if you
    can\'t tell me when you\'re clocking out ahead of time.\n\n
    Me: Never said I would.\n\n
    The Mother: Don\'t you use that tone of voice with me, young man! I have half a mind to ground
    your insolence!\n\n
    Me: You only have half a brain?
    The Mother: That\'s IT! You're grounded as soon as you get home!\n\n
    Me: OPE! Looks like I won\'t be making it home tonight. I\'ve got a company retreat I\'m
    required to attend.\n\n
    The Mother: COMPANY RETREAT ME ASS! You better get your ass home after work or so help me\.\.\.!\n\n
    Me: No can do, madre. The bus it already here.\n\n
    The Mother: YOU STAY PUT! I\'m coming over there right now!\n\n
    Me: Wait, does that mean I can get off work early?\n\n
    The Mother: \.\.\.</string>
    <string name="conversation_3">This is the third conversation.\n\n
    If you couldn\'t tell by now, I couldn\'t really care less what it says.\n\n
    I barely care enough to use proper grammar at this point.\n\n
    I just need a lot of lines.\n\n
    This way I can scroll my scrollView.\n\n
    ScrollView is pretty cool.\n\n
    Especially when you put layouts with extra crap in them.\n\n
    It can make your program super diverse and interesting to look at.\n\n
    Unlike this text you\'re reading.\n\n
    This text is NOT cool or interesting to read.\n\n
    If you\'ve found this conversation and are still reading it\.\.\.\n\n
    just know how amazed I am.\n\n
    I can\'t think of any logical reason anyone would read this far down this \"conversation\"\n\n
    Are you really still reading this?\n\n
    What will it take to get you to stop reading this useless text?\n\n
    I already told you nothing\'s going to happen.\n\n
    Please stop reading\.\.\.\n\n
    Please?\n\n
    Okay, I asked nicely.\n\n
    I\'m gonna start getting nasty if you don\'t stop reading ASAP!\n\n
    I\'m warning you buddy!\n\n
    Seriously, you\'re gonna get it\.\.\.\n\n
    And you\'re not gonna like it!\n\n
    HERE IT COMES!\n\n
    Aight, I don't have anything.\n\n
    You called my bluff.\n\n
    Sorry for being such a dick :(</string>
</resources>